<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>School on Good Debate</title>
    <link>https://gooddebate.org/tags/school/</link>
    <description>Recent content in School on Good Debate</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Feb 15th, 1946. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 03:06:09 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gooddebate.org/tags/school/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Improving the School System</title>
      <link>https://gooddebate.org/tech/improving_school_system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2017 03:06:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gooddebate.org/tech/improving_school_system/</guid>
      <description>Improving the School System I recently came across an essay I wrote my senior year in high school entitled &amp;ldquo;How to improve the educational system&amp;rdquo;. This is one of the longest essays I&amp;rsquo;ve ever written at 5400 words, but it wasn&amp;rsquo;t for a class. I wrote the paper because I felt it would help improve the system if the right people read it. It was well received and made its way up the ladder, unfortunately not much came of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Collection &amp; Ethics</title>
      <link>https://gooddebate.org/tech/data_collection___ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 13:38:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gooddebate.org/tech/data_collection___ethics/</guid>
      <description>Data Collection &amp;amp; Ethics ​	Note: This article might seem odd, it was an assignment for a class that I thought was well written enough to post here. It&amp;rsquo;s a long form ethical post. Enjoy
​	Data collection is an important and highly relevant topic in the modern age. People have wrestled with the degree to which companies control user data for decades, and the world is final starting to see 3 major breaks in ideology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scripts Sites and School</title>
      <link>https://gooddebate.org/tech/scripts_sites_and_school/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 13:35:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gooddebate.org/tech/scripts_sites_and_school/</guid>
      <description>Scripts Sites and School February already!
It&amp;rsquo;s been just over a month since my last post. Don&amp;rsquo;t be mistaken though, I currently have 4 articles waiting to edit including
 Finding and fixing rouge &amp;lsquo;smart&amp;rsquo; routers on an enterprise network Installing and setting up the Skylines Project Part 1 of the Fuzzing series A long-form article about ethics in data collection, retention, and analysis.  Now you may be thinking that&amp;rsquo;s a lot of articles to have waiting for editing and you&amp;rsquo;d be right; I enjoy writing, I do not enjoy editing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
